Washingtoniana Periodicals Collection Periodicals
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
- Washington Informer, 1997-01 - 1997-12 (Box W163)
- Washington Informer, 1998-01 - 1998-12 (Box W164)
- Washington Informer, 1999-01 - 1999-12 (Box W165)
- Washington Informer, 2007-01 - 2011-05 (Box W166)
- Washington Informer, 2011-06 - 2012-12 (Box W167)
- Washington Informer, 2013-01 - 2014-03 (Box W168)
- Washington Informer, 2014-04 - 2015-12 (Box W169)
- Washington Informer, 2016-01 - 2016-10-27 (Box W170)
- Washington International, 1993-01 - 1999-08 (Box W171)
- Washington Jewish Review, 1935 - 1937 (Box W172)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1971-01 - 1971-12 (Box W173)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1972-01 - 1972-12 (Box W174)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1973-01 - 1973-12 (Box W175)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1974-01 - 1974-12 (Box W176)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1975-01 - 1975-12 (Box W177)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1976-01 - 1976-12 (Box W178)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1977-01 - 1977-12 (Box W179)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1978-01 - 1978-12 (Box W180)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1979-01 - 1980-12 (Box W181)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1981-01 - 1982-12 (Box W182)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1983-01 - 1983-06 (Box W183)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1983-07 - 1983-12 (Box W184)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1984-01 - 1984-04 (Box W185)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1984-06 - 1984-08 (Box W186)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1984-09 - 1984-12 (Box W187)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1985-01 - 1985-04 (Box W188)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1985-05 - 1985-07 (Box W189)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1985-10 - 1985-12 (Box W190)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1986-01 - 1986-04 (Box W191)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1986-05 - 1986-08 (Box W192)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1986-09 - 1986-12 (Box W193)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1987-01 - 1987-04 (Box W194)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1987-05 - 1987-08 (Box W195)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1987-09 - 1987-12 (Box W196)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1988-01 - 1988-03 (Box W197)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1988-04 - 1988-07 (Box W198)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1989-01 - 1989-06 (Box W199)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1989-07 - 1989-12 (Box W200)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1990-01 - 1990-06 (Box W201)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1990-07 - 1990-12 (Box W202)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1991-07 - 1991-12 (Box W204)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1992-01 - 1992-06 (Box W205)
- Washington Jewish Week, 1992-07 - 1992-12 (Box W206)
- Washington Jewish Week, 2002-05 - 2003-09 (Box W207)
- Washington Jewish Week, 2006-06 - 2007-12 (Box W208)
- Washington Jewish Week, 2008-01 - 2009-06 (Box W209)
- Washington Jewish Week, 2009-07 - 2010-12 (Box W210)
- Washington Jewish Week, 2011-01 - 2012-12 (Box W211)
- Washington Jewish Week, 2013-01 - 2014-12 (Box W212)
- Washington Jewish Week, 2015-01 - 2017-03-09 (Box W213)
- Washington Lawyer, 1986 - 2000 (Box W214)
- Washington Lawyer, 2001 - 2012 (Box W215)
- Washington Lawyer, 2013 - 2014-05 (Box W216)
- Washington Life, 1903 - 1905 (Box W217)
- Washington Life Magazine, 1991 - 2007 (Box W218)
- Washington Life Magazine, 2008 - 2013 (Box W219)
- Washington Life Magazine, 2014 - 2017-03 (Box W220)
- Washington Medical Annals, 1902 - 1917 (Box W221)
- Washington Newsworks, 1976-02 - 1976-10 (Box W222)
- Washington Observer, The, 1971 - 1973 (Box W223)
- Washington Observer, The, 1974 - 1975 (Box W224)
- Washington Observer, The, 1976 - 1982 (Box W225)
- Washington Observer, The, 1983 - 1998 (Box W226)
- Washington Opera Magazine, The, 1979 - 2004 (Box W227)
- Washington Parent, 2003-04 - 2006-04 (Box W228)
- Washington Parent, 2006-05 - 2009-12 (Box W229)
- Washington Parent, 2010-01 - 2017-02 (Box W230)
- Washington Post Magazine, 1989 - 1990-12 (Box W231)
- Washington Post Magazine, 1991-01 - 1993-06 (Box W232)
- Washington Post Magazine, 1993-07 - 1995-12 (Box W233)
- Washington Print Club Quarterly, The, 2007 - 2011 (Box W234)
- Washington Real Estate Board News, 1946-01 - 1953-12 (Box W235)
- Washington Realtor, 1931-04 - 1945-12 (Box W236)
- Washington Review, 1974 - 1978 (Box W237)
- Washington Review, 1979 - 1983 (Box W238)
- Washington Review, 1984 - 1988 (Box W239)
- Washington Review, 1990 - 1992 (Box W240)
- Washington Review, 1993 - 1994 (Box W241)
- Washington Review, 1995 - 1996 (Box W242)
- Washington Review, 1997 - 1999 (Box W243)
- Washington Review, 2000 - 2002 (Box W244)
- Washington Sun, 1988 - 1994 (Box W245)
- Washington Sun, 1995 - 1995 (Box W246)
- Washington Sun, 1996 - 1997 (Box W247)
- Washington Sun, 1998 - 1998 (Box W248)
- Washington Sun, 1999 - 1999 (Box W249)
- Washington Sun, 2000 - 2000 (Box W250)
- Washington Sun, 2001 - 2001 (Box W251)
- Washington Sun, 2002-01 - 2002-08 (Box W252)
- Washington Sun, 2002-09 - 2003-06 (Box W253)
- Washington Sun, 2003-07 - 2003-10 (Box W254)
- Washington Sun, 2003-11 - 2004-07 (Box W255)
- Washington Sun, 2004-08 - 2005-08 (Box W256)
- Washington Sun, 2005-08 - 2006-05 (Box W257)
- Washington Sun, 2006-06 - 2006-10 (Box W258)
- Washington Sun, 2009-05 - 2015-04 (Box W259)
- Washington Techway, 2000-01 - 2000-12 (Box W260)
- Washington Techway, 2001-01 - 2001-05 (Box W261)
- Washington Tribune, 1978 - 1981 (Box W262)
- Washington Tribune, 1982 - 1984 (Box W263)
- Washingtonian, 1969 - 1971 (Box W264)
- Washingtonian, 1972 - 1976 (Box W265)
- Washingtonian, 1976 - 1979 (Box W266)
- Washingtonian, 1979 - 1982 (Box W267)
- Washingtonian, 1982 - 1985-09 (Box W268)
- Washingtonian, 1985-10 - 1987-09 (Box W269)
- Washingtonian, 1988-01 - 1990-01 (Box W270)
- Washingtonian, 1990-02 - 1992-03 (Box W271)
- Washingtonian, 1992-04 - 1995-12 (Box W272)
- Washingtonian, 1996-01 - 1997-12 (Box W273)
- Washingtonian, 1998-01 - 2000-07 (Box W274)
- Washingtonian, 2000-07 - 2002-12 (Box W275)
- Washingtonian, 2002-01 - 2005-06 (Box W276)
- Washingtonian, 2005-07 - 2006-12 (Box W277)
- Washingtonian, 2006-07 - 2008-06 (Box W278)
- Washingtonian, 2008-08 - 2011-12 (Box W279)
- Washingtonian, 2012-01 - 2013-12 (Box W280)
- Washingtonian, 2014-01 - 2015-12 (Box W281)
- Washingtonian, 2016-01 - 2017-03 (Box W282)
- Watergate Hotel Review, 1973 - 1976 (Box W283)
- WCA Nonprofit Agenda, 1993-01 - 2000-12 (Box W284)
- WCA Nonprofit Agenda, 2001-01 - 2003-12 (Box W285)
- Where Washington, 1991-10 - 1994-04 (Box W286)
- Where Washington, 1995-02 - 1996-12 (Box W287)
- Where Washington, 1997-01 - 1998-11 (Box W288)
- Where Washington, 1999-01 - 2000-09 (Box W289)
- Where Washington, 2000-10 - 2002-06 (Box W290)
- Where Washington, 2002-07 - 2003-12 (Box W291)
- Where Washington, 2004-01 - 2005-12 (Box W292)
- Where Washington, 2006-01 - 2010-12 (Box W293)
- Where Washington, 2011-01 - 2017-03 (Box W294)
- Woman's Monthly, 1992-09 - 2002-12 (Box W295)
- Women's Club City Bulletin, 1921 - 1931 (Box W296)
- Wonder Flame, 1947 - 1973 (Box W297)
- Wood Thrush, 1948-08 - 1950-08 (Box W298)
- Wood Wind, 1971-01 - 1973-11 (Box W299)
- W - Misc 1 (Box W300)
- Washington City Paper, 1998-01 - 1998-12 (Box w301)
- Washington City Paper, 1999-01 - 1999-07 (Box W302)
- Washington City Paper, 1999-08 - 2000-04 (Box W303)
- Washington City Paper, 2000-05 - 2000-12 (Box W304)
- Washington City Paper, 2001-01 - 2001-12 (Box W305)
- Washington City Paper, 2002-01 - 2002-12 (Box W306)
- Washington City Paper, 2003-01 - 2003-12 (Box W307)
- Washington City Paper, 2004-01 - 2004-12 (Box W308)
- Washington City Paper, 2005-01 - 2005-12 (Box W309)
- Washington City Paper, 2006-01 - 2006-12 (Box W310)
- Washington City Paper, 2007-01 - 2007-12 (Box W311)
- Washington City Paper, 2008-01 - 2010-12 (Box W312)
- Washington City Paper, 2011-01 - 2011-12 (Box W313)
- Washington City Paper, 2012-01 - 2012-12 (Box W314)
- Washington City Paper, 2013-01 - 2013-12 (Box W315)
- Washington City Paper, 2014-01 - 2014-12 (Box W316)
- Washington City Paper, 2015-01 - 2015-12 (Box W317)
- Washington Hispanic, 2011-07 - 2011-12 (Box W318)
- Washington City Paper, 1981-01 - 1982-12 (Box W319)
- Young DC, 1991 - 1998 (Box Y001)
- Young DC, 1999 - 2008 (Box Y002)
- Zoogoer, 1972 - 1981 (Box Z001)
- Zoogoer, 1984 - 1997 (Box Z002)
- Zoogoer, 1998 - 2016 (Box Z003)